Nikita: Mom?
Mom: Nikita, when am I going to eat?
Nikita: I'm deaf and can't hear you.
Mom: Turn it off.
Nikita: I'll just finish watching it.
Mom: Get up!
Mom: Good morning.
Mom: Please brush your teeth and have breakfast.
Katya: Mom, it's the holidays, Zhenya.
Mom: So what? If you lie in bed all day, what will happen?
Katya: Apocalypse.
Katya: The regime will collapse.
Mom: Get up!
Mom: Dad!
Grandpa: Are you spying on your own father?
Mom: Why would I spy on him?
Mom: The breakfast is ready. Let's go.
Grandpa: It's okay.
Grandpa: I'll take care of myself somehow.
Mom: Good morning, dad.
Grandpa: Why are you looking at me like that?
Grandpa: I can't live without you.
Grandpa: I really can't
Katya: Nikita, could you leave me alone?
Katya: Mom, Nikita ate all the cotton again.
Nikita: It's not cotton, it's balls.
Nikita: You wouldn't know you don't even eat this.
Mom: Please be quiet! I am on a roll with migraine
Dad: Sveta!
Mom: Yes!!
Mom: And I'm on a roll with starvation, mom.
Dad: Sveta!
Katya: Cereal!?
Katya: Mom, I won't eat this!
Mom: If you want some fried eggs then fry them yourself.
Katya: You know, I'll just burn everything and you'll get the migraine again.
Nikita: Dad, how about we go visiting our Estamosthoi people?
Dad: What Estamosthoi people? You know, I'm working until it's dark.
Dad: Go and see your Grandpa.
Dad: Sveta, please help.
Dad: Sveta, help me. I feel like I have a snake hanging here.
Katya: Dad, are you in a corporation or what?
Mom: We have a promotion.
Dad: You know, I wouldn't be so sure. We still have to ask him.
Mom: Be sure and be positive. You'll succeed.
Potapov: What did he say?
Potapov Henchman: Some promotion.
Potapov: Is he out of his mind?
Potapov: Are you out of your mind?
Dad: A regular promotion. But in the future.
Potapov: In what future?
Dad: In the near future. I've thought about it. How to attract new investments.
Potapov: Investments?
Potapov: I didn't have time to read about the past investments.
Potapov: And they're already coming to me from Moscow with a check.
Potapov: That's good.
Potapov: Good people have time to warn.
Potapov: They first went to bloggers, and now to honest entrepreneurs.
Potapov: Where did they come from?
Potapov: And what can I show them?
Potapov: A hole from the public? That's it?
Potapov: We tried, at least.
Potapov: But I'm sorry to have to tell you that...
Potapov: I'm closing our project.
Popatov Henchman: Artak Seminovich, did you decide for sure?
Popatov: There's nowhere to decide.
Popatov: Get ready.
Wow! What is this?
Meteorite?
Grandpa, the meteorite fell right behind our village.
Well, I saw it. Is it a trace from the plane?
No, it's definitely a meteorite. I saw it.
Let's go and see.
What if we present the model again?
And the fact that the terms have moved, well, let's say, we've reworked everything inside.
I won't pay 2 billion for the model.
We've already shown the model twice. They'll just put me in third place.
What if...
What if? What?
No ifs.
Well...
Well, we didn't manage to do it with you, the taxi-flying guy.
Well, who could have thought that it would turn out like this?
And Moscow didn't manage to do it either.
There are no such technologies. Where can we get them?
These technologies.
That's it.
Come on.
Ah.
Goodbye.
Come on.
No.
There we go.
Iven.
Woah, woah.
Try again.
Even more looks.
There.
Wait.
That's it.
Help me!
Come on, drag me down!
Come on, grab me faster!
What was that just now?
What?
What is this thing?
How do I know?
Maybe it fell off our space station?
It's obviously high-tech.
We need to find out where it came from.
Hi, Dad!
Hi. Did you have a day off?
Yeah, I did.
I don't want to rest.
Okay, bye.
Those parts, okay?
And here, the meteorite falls in the forest in search of grapes.
If you go to our forest and find out where it went down from,
that'll take you.
What is this even?
The meteorite of the Space Station or Glacier on Poisonous Legs.
Ahead!
Right.
We will be the richest! Hooray!
Excuse me, citizen, have you seen anything strange here?
They say a meteorite has fallen somewhere here.
Men, do I look like an astronomer?
I'm not surprised, you know.
First, they poked us with 5G towers everywhere.
Then the satellites began to descend from the orbit.
The towers have nothing to do with it.
It's a meteorite rain. Perseids.
Maloy, what are Perseids?
Every year in August our planet passes through a stream of water.
How much do you pay for a meteorite?
Not much. We'll find it ourselves.
Listen, kid, what house are you from?
I'm not from any house.
I'm an Asian, baby. Hip-hop, I'm livin' it.
This hip-hop, livin' it.
I say I'm livin' it.
Here we go.
You know how we go.
One time for your mind.
We gon' shine.
Sit back.
Put my life on wax.
Oh, shit.
Analytics.
I shall get your blood refreshed.
Ooh!
I sould do it!
You might see Snorp radio.
How about this picture?
Oh, come on!
What the hell is this?
What happened to Snorp.
The poor thing is out.
Let's go!
Come on.
The boy wants to go shopping for sugar Doctor.
And the old lady, one for her.
Stop, boy, stop!
Greetings to you, earthling.
Put down my barrel, please.
Wow.
Don't be afraid, baby.
I won't touch you.
What baby? I'm almost 13.
I'm Nikita.
And who are you?
Hello, Nikita.
My full name is...
Who?
May I call you Jdun?
Jdun?
Well, okay.
What are you doing here?
My platoon was hit by a meteorite.
I had to make a hard landing.
Here? In the swamp?
Yes.
I'm unlucky.
It's so low, I haven't fallen yet.
What kind of ship is it?
It's my platoon scout.
For long flights.
Nikita, can you help me to pull out the ship?
We'll try.
But you need to be well prepared.
Huh?
What's that?
Jdun, you can't stay here.
It's getting dark.
And they can find you.
Huh? No, no, no.
No, I'm going to the camp.
I'm shit!
Hold that.
I live there.
Alone?
Do other pebs live there?
Some pebs live here too.
Katya, my sister.
Mom, dad, grandpa.
But he stayed in his workshop when granny died.
He doesn't want to be with us.
Mom says he has depression.
Nikita, is this your brass?
Do you use it, too?
No, it's not my brass. It's just a toy.
A toy?
I think you'll like mine.
I like toys.
I like them very much.
But they're not ready yet.
It's a rare toy, of course.
Nikita, you can't tell anyone about me.
I have a secret mission.
Wow. What is it?
You have a very rare mineral.
Our ancient people said it was on Earth.
And I came here to find out.
I thought you were just sitting and waiting.
Not just that. Sometimes we eat and wait.
I don't know what we're waiting for.
Someday I'll find out what we're waiting for and eat it all.
It's about the same on Earth.
All right, we'll save your planet.
Oh.
Look, we do this when we make a deal.
And when we say hello.
Well, hello, Nikita.
Well, hello, Dad.
Hello, Katya.
Did they send you to a remote today?
Well, something like that.
Snorp, knock it off.
Ouch.
Nikita, wait for me.
This is my sister, Katya. Don't be afraid.
Nikita, did you tell them about me?
Hide me, baby, faster, please.
Daddy.
Baby, can you see me?
Yes.
My grandfather and I won the lottery.
So what did you want? I don't have much time.
He doesn't have much time.
I wanted to offer you to go to the lake.
But they are looking for interns on TV again.
Well, everything is as always.
We'll come, we'll come up with something.
You are the cameraman, I am the star.
No!
What do you mean, no?
Can't you find your own sister for an hour?
I'm just...
Katya...
Fu!
You yourself are fu!
When did you have time to be so rude?
Katya, I...
Let's go.
Katya, I still have business here and all that.
Well, look at him, business man.
Just ask me to give your Vika flowers at least once more.
Got it?
Thank you for your help, brother!
I'm waiting.
We don't eat like this on Earth.
Nikita, I haven't eaten for an hour.
So what didn't you tell me?
I'll come back now, I'll bring you something to eat.
Just sit here and don't touch anything.
Okay.
It's all fu.
And on our planet I eat every hour.
It's Adaptive
Evgeny, you got it?
The only thing I can do is hold you there.
I've been waiting for you.
Nikita, where have you been all this time?
I've been sitting here and there. I've been starving.
I haven't eaten this much when I was your age.
If you've just arrived today, tell me, where did we get your photos?
Here. And one of the artists even made your sculpture. Look.
Wow! So he really was here.
Nikita, this is our wise Snorp Starun.
He told me about the shalalalala mineral on your Earth.
By the way, why do you need this mineral?
Shalalalala is a rare mineral.
Nikita, thanks to its properties, we are long-living people.
I see.
Thank you.
We can eat for a long time and wait for a long time.
Wow!
Nikita, when are we going to take the ship out?
Tonight.
Just don't make any noise, okay?
Come in, Snorp.
Thank you.
Nikita, what is this place?
Quiet!
Is someone waiting for us here?
In grandpa's workshop.
He used to be an engineer.
Golden hands.
He even registered several inventions for his institute.
But when granny died, he abandoned everything.
Oh! Like our wise Snorp Starun.
Snorp!
Quiet!
Guys!
Beshenstvo!
O, red flag!
Red stars!
We can't go home!
Us?
No.
Come.
We don't have a thing to lose.
Where is our thing?
Let's go.
Yes, let's go.
What do we need?
The general and rope.
It's a rare place.
I probably forgot to tell you, but the ship weighs 67 times more than you.
Are you sure you can do it?
I'm not sure. Help me. I can't do it alone.
Okay. Although I usually wait.
Nikita, I think we need another hundred earthlings.
Someone's coming! Look!
Kurokaki!
Hurry up and hide!
Where?
Over here!
Okay.
Sit here.
I'll go.
Kostya, look. What's there?
Where?
Look.
Nikita!
Grandpa?
Nikita! Oh, my God! What are you doing?
Where did you run off to, huh?
It's some kind of garbage.
Grandpa, we're pulling out an airstrike here.
An airstrike?
Yes, with him.
Can you imagine if... Mom...
Greetings to you, wise earthly old man.
I'm not that old.
All right, then, wise young man.
Georgiy Evgenievich, can I just... Goga?
Hello, just Goga. I'm...
Can I just wait?
Can I just...
I've always known that we're not alone in the universe.
No, you're not alone in the universe.
What?
What should we do with all this now?
Arkady Semyonovich, I'm sorry it's late.
We've been looking for you for a day, but there's nothing.
Maybe everything really burned down in the atmosphere.
Well, you know, like...
Perseids.
You hear me, Zalkovsky?
You're going to send your Perseids to the planetarium.
I don't care how you find this alien shit.
If someone gets ahead of us, I'll send you to the moon myself.
No connection.
Well?
We need to look for him.
Let's go.
Step back to a safe distance.
Commencing evacuation.
Optimists.
They wanted to pull us out with their hands.
Step back.
Now.
Step...
Step down to earth like you used to be.
You think you can trick me into doing it?
And you?
But mom, do you know?
Yes, mom, do you know?
Okay.
We didn't see each other.
Here. We were on the verge of failure.
And ran away.
Thanks to my stubbornness.
And mine.
I agree. Come on, take it.
Come on, come on, a little bit.
You're a bastard.
The energy circuit of the ship is damaged.
Now just give it to the scrap metal.
Goga, don't give it to the scrap metal.
It must be repaired to return to the family.
I'm waiting. What's this button?
You can't.
It's an intergalactic diminution.
It's very dangerous for the Earth.
Look!
Look at this hole!
Where is the hole?
Be careful.
It's not a hole. It's a technical hole.
What is it?
It's an anti-gravity connector. It's launching my platoon.
Oh, no! Kurakaka! The anti-gravity is gone! My platoon can't fly without it!
Stop panicking.
So, Nikita is looking for a detail.
I'll replace the wiring. We'll make holes and that's it.
Are you sure this platoon can handle it?
Grandpa, are we sure we can do it?
What?
It's good that we didn't let our children go to the scrapyard.
Well, did you want a wonder of technology?
You'll bite it.
Call the city committee. And call the mayor, too. We'll take part.
We'll show them a flying taxi.
Sveta, I still need to fill in the papers.
Let's go, let's go.
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
Sveta.
Congratulations!
What for? The cake must be expensive.
Of course, it's expensive. It's for the financial director.
You're the best!
Tell us, please, how Potap praised your presentation.
What's there to tell?
Go tell Semyonov.
For the promotion.
And your presentation, he says.
On the wall. There, hang it.
I didn't hesitate for a second.
Really?
Not a second.
That's why he ordered us a new kitchen.
Well, I understand, of course, it's not the cheapest project, but it's no worse than Lytyagin's.
Have you seen how huge their built-in cabinets are?
Listen, Populya, since you're buying a new kitchen for Mom, can I have a new phone?
And I need a new bike.
But if I'm going to be a journalist, I need to shoot quality videos.
What journalist? We've already talked about it.
You need to be an economist.
You'll be a manager like your dad, and you'll have a good salary.
Mom.
Make a salary after her.
The last one. Especially when you don't work yourself.
You'll thank your mother later.
Can I say thank you now, and I'll do whatever I want to do?
All right. I'll go to bed.
Thank you for your help.
Thank you for the cake.
Misha, with a promotion.
And with a new kitchen.
Dad, can you sit down for a bit?
No, no, no. I want to sleep.
Don't be upset. Look, we'll get more.
Everyone doesn't like it. Let's do it again.
Okay.
Hello, everyone. It's me, young reporter Yekaterina Semyonova.
This is my vlog from the solar system in Dursun.
Today the sun pleases me with its warmth,
and so I decided to sunbathe a little.
Well, of course, with sunscreens from tanning.
This is a direct connection.
I've been thought of something.
I'll keep you informed of the events.
I'll be back in a minute.
But if there are any vacancies,
please keep me in mind.
I'm in touch 24 hours a day.
I have many years of experience.
Higher economic education.
Two.
So I can run start-ups,
a well-developed business.
No vacancies, right?
I got it. Thank you.
Goodbye.
Seryozha, hi.
Here, take it.
You gave it to me.
I'm glad to see you, Yevgenievich.
We haven't seen each other for a hundred years.
Are you going to make something out of grandpa?
No, we...
Yes.
We're going to make an antenna.
An antenna for further communication.
Not a thing.
Hello, Yevgenievich.
I'm going to take a picture of you.
I'll take you to the restaurant.
You're a good man, Yevgenievich.
Good.
I'll be back.
I'll be back in a minute.
Bye.
See you.
Bye-bye.
Bye.
See you, Yevgenievich.
See you.
Bye.
Let's take a look over here.
This is what I was thinking about.
How much is it?
Hide it, hide it.
There's a golden vein here.
Here.
Thank you.
Hey!
Dad?
Dad, look, there's a dad.
What dad?
What do you want?
I wanted to give you some ice cream.
I don't take lactose.
I'm sorry.
Dad!
What? Are you not working again?
The lunch, son.
I came to take a walk, to get some fresh air.
Fresh air?
Dad got overheated. He bought two whole ice creams.
Let's go, Nikitos.
Georgievich.
Nikitos, we need to be extremely careful.
Yes. Dad almost burned us.
What am I talking about?
That no one should know about it.
Hi.
You're back, quiet people.
I thought I wouldn't guess that something was going on here.
I'm sorry, Nikita. I was bitten again.
Why didn't you tell me about Snorp?
He's so cool.
By the way, you didn't know that he likes lemons.
But we left you here for only two hours.
You can't be so reliable and tell everyone everything.
Katya, I beg you, don't tell anyone about Snorp.
Some people were looking for him.
What's wrong with such cars?
Relax, little one.
Katya.
What Katya? I've been here for 15 years.
Did you really not tell anyone?
I'm silent like a dead Cambala.
Cambala. Katya is cool.
She jokes and likes to eat like me.
Okay, don't get distracted.
He said that he urgently needs some detail.
He needs a detail.
Now help him.
Okay.
That's it.
Start please.
One moment.
Extra.
What?
No, it's not too much.
Good. A screwdriver.
A screwdriver.
Good job. You remembered.
Cool.
A sidecutter.
Yes, a sidecutter.
Oh, I remembered.
You remembered.
There's a sidecutter.
A sidecutter.
No, no, it's not a sidecutter.
It's an air blower.
I'm sorry.
It blows.
And this...
An air blower.
This is an air blower.
It's an air blower.
Stop.
Don't move east!
Stop there!
Don't move!
Stop!
Don't!
Don't move east!
Don't move!
Where are they now?
Hello, Georgiy Evgenievich.
Hello.
There's a case here.
I wanted to ask you not to tell Sveta
that you saw me in the city one day.
Or else she might have...
Yes?
And you mean... nothing?
No, nothing.
I mean...
I don't know.
Me?
I'm fine, Georgiy Evgenievich.
I...
I wanted to ask Sveta to come here.
Is that Nikita?
He found an antigravitin...
That's it. We're here.
What?
What is it?
Dad, does he like you?
Yes.
Can someone explain to me what's going on here?
Is he really from space?
Be quiet, dad. Or mom will hear us.
Yes, dad, be quiet.
Mom will hear us and call the police.
There's a problem with the registration.
What? Yes, dad. We have aliens.
What's going on?
Listen...
We helped Mom fix the stardust.
Yes, dad.
Dad, look what a cool stardust.
What?
Shh!
Are you there?
Guys!
That's it.
Dad! No! No!
What's going on?
Let's go.
Wow!
Look, Sveta.
What are you doing?
Look what we have here.
Son, step aside.
Dad, please.
Your stardust.
It's an alien.
Yes.
Nikita got it for the new school year.
So to speak, from scrap metal and all that garbage.
In the style of steampunk, right?
Yes. In what style?
Steampunk.
Like postmodernism, but only steampunk, mom.
There are sculptures of all sorts of junk.
And we help.
And you help Nikita.
Yes. My own brother and grandfather help after all.
Of course, steampunk. It's all ours.
Can I look at it?
No, not yet.
There are wires there, mom. No need.
Is there a cabin there?
There will be a cabin and devices.
It's just that there's nothing to show now.
Isn't it dangerous?
It's dangerous.
Very.
Listen, mom, you need to help with something.
Let me help.
I can peel potatoes, cut lettuce and wash dishes.
Come on.
Then you go and we'll catch up with you.
Come on, catch up.
Come on.
Dad, thank you.
Come on, let's go in order.
Grandpa and I are going to get the wires.
Yes, get the wires. Because I don't have enough of them.
Listen, Nikita, let's go to the sea.
Or we can go to the Northern Vynogradniks,
because we haven't searched there yet.
It's very crowded there.
Good morning.
Good morning. Hello.
Hello, mom.
It's the weekend. You've already got up and had breakfast.
Dad has started running. I don't recognize you.
Sport is life and peace.
Yes. Yes. We grow and develop.
Yes, mom.
I've got a surprise for you, too.
What is it?
Today we're going on a sea trip.
I've already bought the tickets,
so no objections.
That's great, mom.
Thank you very much.
Wonderful surprise.
Thank you, mom.
Mom, thank you very much.
Thank you.
Mom, look how beautiful it is.
Oh, how beautiful it is here.
Yes, but this village has one drawback.
What drawback?
You can't leave everything and go to the sea.
Grandpa, let's go.
Listen, mom,
we didn't go on vacation because of this drawback.
By the way, Ksyusha
is already in Maldives with her parents.
And her parents are in Spain.
While we're relaxing here,
we're waiting for the one who's sad
and waiting for help.
Guys, by the way, did you leave him something to eat?
What is he eating?
I left him a chocolate bar.
It will be enough for two hours.
In the kitchen?
Yes.
This one?
What are you doing here?
To keep a secret?
We're keeping a secret.
We're not going anywhere.
And grandpa hasn't been with us for a long time.
Yes, grandpa.
You haven't been with us for a long time.
A long time, yes.
Mom, why did you leave?
Let's take some more pictures.
You'll be a queen.
Will the king go to take pictures with me?
Yes.
Let's go.
The clock is ticking, and the clock is ticking We are waiting for the light and the earth, and we are dreaming
And we are dreaming of the hero of the cosmodrome
And this is not the ice blue
And we are dreaming of the grass, the grass of the home
The green, the green grass
Kurakaka!
Curakaka?
Curakaka,alis!
Curakaks!
According to the family business, do you want alloy, but it does not matter if you offer
The main thing is to offer, right, daughter?
It's a luxury one.
Here it is.
What's this?
Did you steal it?
Call the police.
Calm down, Sveta.
Wait.
Why are you waiting?
Nothing is missing.
I know.
I know, it's these...
homeless, vandals.
They left us an installation.
Yes.
Yes, that's right.
It's a raccoon.
A raccoon?
What raccoon?
It's so wild.
Here.
The window.
Open it.
It goes here.
That's right, it's a raccoon.
And it got in here.
Please, don't touch anything.
Nikita, don't touch anything.
What if it's a sick raccoon?
What if it's mad?
It's my chocolate paste.
Give me your hands.
A raccoon with a bird flu.
Everyone, put on your masks.
That's it.
My head hurts.
Sveta, calm down, I beg you.
Breathe.
It's all right.
The raccoon wanted something sweet.
He smeared it all over here.
Now we'll sweep it all away, wash it away.
Well?
Listen, Mom, don't worry.
I'll wipe it all away, wipe it all away.
Well...
Yes, Mom.
Oh, I told you, it's a raccoon.
Okay, I'll call the wild boar hunting service.
Mom, don't.
Don't.
I'm here.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've checked everything.
You can relax, you don't have any animals.
Thanks, I transferred the money to my card.
Tell me who it was, please.
Not typical for a raccoon, at all.
Someone was much bigger.
A raccoon was bigger.
A mutant.
Or a boar.
A mutant?
But I don't think so. I haven't seen any beavers or mutants.
What if he comes back?
If he comes back, call us.
For now, you'll have to spit in your mouth for self-defense.
Spit in my mouth?
Can you do that?
What? If you do that again, you'll get in contact with the zoo.
Nikita, it's not the time for the zoo.
Look, I've found salt.
Salt?
Salt.
Do you need salt?
Well, this is your rare mineral, salt.
You don't understand, this is salt.
We have a lot of it in every store.
A lot?
I can give you a ton of it.
Why didn't you say anything, Kurokako? Give me salt.
But we have to return the salt.
A lot of salt.
What?
This is my salt mineral.
This is mine.
This is my mother's mineral. She'll be mad. Give it to me.
Give it to me.
I'm waiting.
I'll get you more. I promise.
Nikita, I need to get a lot of salt. Will you help me?
Yes.
A lot of salt.
Very good.
Let me get it out.
ATHENS
They aren't there, though, now.
That apple's not in there.
Yes.
Well, Alya, as you said,
family is a little miracle in the vast universe.
Right?
Right.
Come on, wake up.
I like girly games the most.
As you said, family is a little miracle in the vast universe.
Right?
summarized
Mutant is back.
Go to sleep, Mutant.
You little brat!
Sit down.
Everything is fine.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Do you see this?
Yes.
What is this? Please, call an ambulance.
Mom, calm down. This is our friend.
He is an alien.
What do you mean? Is he a stranger?
Mom, he is not a stranger. Don't exaggerate.
He is very close to us. He is our Dunishka.
This scum has agonized you. Don't touch him.
Sveta, what nonsense is this?
He is completely harmless.
Mom, he is in trouble, and we are helping him.
Don't shout.
We didn't say that you knew him. He is a psycho.
Georgiy Evgenievich. What?
Mom, let's leave him alone.
Look how cool he is.
Please.
Where should we leave him?
Listen, we will repair his ship
and send him home.
Yes, and he will live with grandpa in the barn.
Let's leave him alone. Mom, please.
I will do everything you ask.
Moreover, you said it yourself. We need to help our neighbor.
Yes, Mom. He is a funny man.
He is a harmless creature.
Touch him. He is a very cool creature.
He is very soft. You will really like him.
Mom, he is kind. Don't be afraid.
We are touching him. You will really like him.
He is so soft. He is very good.
Come on.
Please.
Touch him.
Don't be afraid.
He is not scary.
Do you see, Mom?
The fur is moving.
And Snorp is with us.
Let's touch the spend for him.
Listen, Mom. It's okay since it is not bad.
Snorp will be dressed in a kilometameter cloth.
Indeed. Just like aloe.
What?
Just like aloe, Misha?
Just like aloe.
The End
Oh, wake up!
Come on, get up.
Grandpa already fixed the spaceship.
Yes.
Let's go and take a look.
You fixed it so quickly.
Dad, are you coming out too?
Wow. I haven't decided yet.
Thank you for your help.
Without you, I'd just sit and wait for other Earthlings.
What kind of help? We didn't find the gravitational module anyway.
All right, I have to go to work.
And we have to look for the detail. Let's go.
If we can find it, of course.
Wait, who will help me with the washing machine?
Kakaloya.
There will be a deputy minister of transport, and a mayor.
There is also someone from Moscow.
A banquet, a furset, a quartet. Well, as always.
Taxi? Well, of course, it will fly.
It will definitely fly. Where will it go?
We are waiting for you. With my wife. Bye.
See? We got lost.
What is there on TV?
Arkadiy Semenovich.
Zhanna.
Well, can I congratulate you?
With what?
You are our hero of the day. You made a flying taxi.
What?
With these very hands.
Do you feel what it smells like?
What? What does it smell like?
Sensations.
Ah.
Are you sure?
Yes. Let's go and record the interview.
Well, let's go and record it.
Today the world-wide event has entered the browser.
The flight company has created the world's first flying taxi.
Arkadiy Semenovich, tell me, how do you feel?
Louder!
How do you feel?
Excuse me, please do it louder.
I am absolutely delighted.
Despite the fact that no one believed in us.
They laughed at us.
But we still did it.
Even Elon Musk was not able to do it.
And we will show you.
In three days.
Flying taxi.
My name is Potapov.
I will help you.
Your part is with Potapov.
Are you sure?
I am sure.
What?
A week ago, our office did not have any flying taxi in the name.
No, there was one Chinese prototype that Potapov sold in Shanghai.
Ah.
He wanted to redo it.
It was profitable for his development.
Well, there, in fact, is nothing.
So, a motorroller with a motor.
And now it really flies.
And now the question.
George Evgenievich.
Yes, yes.
Could he invent such a miracle of technology in a week, so to speak?
So, if even Chinese technologies did not help him, it is unlikely that he himself will.
So, the part of Potapov?
The real flying taxi.
Here, look.
It is here in Abrao-Dyurso.
The head of the company, Arkadiy Syvenovich Potapov,
the ideologist and the inspirer of this project,
today exclusively showed me this miracle of technology.
Here, welcome to the Citadel of technological thought.
The frontline, the domestic.
Please.
Where are you going?
Send me out of here.
Quiet.
I'll do it myself.
Here.
So, why he stole my anti-gravity pressing…
and inserted into your ugly机 .
Let him come back.
Yeah.
Yes.
He won't give it to me.
If he doesn't show a flying taxi at the exhibition in a week,
he'll settle down at the cost of nothing.
So, you have to return it, Detal.
Good morning.
Hello, everybody.
This is your Special rental company.
C-icias.com
This is a special night report from the very center of the newest technologies.
From the company Ulyot.
And here are our first guests.
Girl, this is a closed territory. What are you doing here?
I'm burning, damn it. I'm a journalist and a blogger.
Okay, that's it. You can't shoot here. Take it away.
Hey! You have no right!
Hey, where are you going? I'm going to throw you in the trash!
This is my property! I'm not going anywhere!
Come on, let's go.
The item is here.
Okay.
Grandpa! Grandpa!
What?
Where are you going?
Grandpa!
Hold him! Hold him!
What's wrong?
How did you turn it on?
I don't know.
Can I do it again?
I'll give it to you again.
Let's get out of here.
Come on.
Not there. Where did you come from? There's a alarm.
What alarm? You didn't say anything about the alarm.
I'm talking about the alarm and about the cameras.
You just don't listen to me.
Stop it! Turn off the light!
Semyonov and his team!
Well?
In this round you won...
Well, of course, you didn't do anything wrong.
Because in your gorgeous plan there is one flaw.
This is a video surveillance camera, which has filmed your intrusion and theft of private property.
This is not your part.
Is it yours?
How will you prove it?
And in general, you, brave boy.
You will sing at our orphanage.
Together with your sister.
And your grandfather in the orphanage.
Oh my God!
Mishka.
Do you really take revenge on me because I fired you?
You were fired?
So you're lying to your wife?
Well, not good, not good.
Mishka is a liar.
Okay, tell me.
Why do you need my part?
Who sent you here?
No one sent us here.
We just wanted to help Snorp fix the star.
What?
Who is Snorp?
Who?
Snorp is his grandfather.
It's his surname.
I am Snorp.
He is just a pilot.
And he built a ship.
And this is his part.
So you want to say...
Yes.
That the ship from which this part fell off was always with you?
No.
Semenov, I have a great offer for you.
So in the end, are you Mishka or Volkov?
Well, okay.
Listen, give me your father.
You are Snorp to me or take the plate.
And I am your family.
Dad, please, don't give Snorp.
Friends can't be betrayed, dad.
Dad.
Please, dad.
No, don't.
Yes, dad, don't.
Misha, turn your head at least once.
He said your father was not from the programme激 sizes at all.
He could be your father, I am looking for his family.
But if that is so, he belongs to you.
To his father?
To your grandfather?
Is he a family or some animal from space?
Take it, take it.
Here.
Something happened?
And where is Nikita? Katya?
Just Goga?
They will take you to Nikita.
I see.
I have a whole bottle of Royale here.
And an alien.
And a flying ship.
Yes.
Semyonov, you know how to cheer me up.
Let Semyonov go.
Have a good day.
I'm sorry, friend.
It's my fault.
Load it.
I did something wrong.
It's all right.
Welcome to Earth.
What for?
Wait.
Good.
Analytics.
We should be able to do it.
Well, I agree.
Let us do it.
This is the path to the end of the hypnosis.
It is impossible to conhece the behavior of such individuals.
Yes, I understand.
But what about you?
You should know well, too.
Let's go.
Hope leaves the last one.
I agree.
But under one condition.
If you have this hope.
Oh, my God.
Well, how is your gravitsapp working?
I don't understand what you're talking about, earthling.
Judging by your appearance and IQ level,
you're hardly any different from an inflated sofa.
Teach your ship how to control it.
No. I want to see Nikita.
Listen, inflated palm, I give you one minute.
If you don't explain how this thing flies,
I'll take your Nikita and his whole family and make it hurt a lot.
No, no, don't.
I'll teach you how to fly.
What's worse?
How I Courtyard Tony Какoutov
Yes, I have lied to you.
You know why?
Because you guys aren't as close as you are.
Are you a good friend, dad? You're a good friend. You discuss everything.
You've been digging in your barn for three years and you don't get out of it.
What's wrong with you?
Mom, you said it yourself. Grandpa has depression.
What depression? It was just very hard for me. That's all.
Dad, it was hard for everyone. We all lost a loved one.
But we continue to live somehow.
We made a room for you. The biggest one in the house. For you.
Again.
Again, dad. You don't want to talk to anyone. You haven't been out of it for three years.
What's wrong with you? What's wrong with you? I'm an adult.
Calm down.
No, let's discuss. Dad asks us to discuss.
Are we kids?
I can do whatever I want.
Grandpa, stop it. Mom, dad, stop behaving like kids.
We're all one family. And now our friend is in trouble.
He believed us, but we betrayed him.
Do they do that?
We have to fix it.
I'll tie you up. You said it well. Good boy.
Right. Right. Right.
What's wrong with you?
Go.
Zhanna! Hello. Come on in, please.
To the stage. Play some music. Where are you dragging the table?
Back. To the stage.
Guys, we don't have time for a walk. Bring some drinks.
What kind of car is this? What kind of car is this?
This?
What kind of company is this?
The sweetest. Space desserts.
Everything is here.
Postcards, product checks, composition and a list of desserts.
Very good.
Bring a cake and a tablecloth for the market.
Don't look at the water, kid.
What sensation did you prepare for us?
I can't tell you anything yet, but the report will be a bomb.
But you can come on air on my team, please. Thank you.
The
This is a diver. I'm on the spot.
Yes, I'm on the spot.
They changed the key. Let's go through the basement.
Wait, the window is open. I can get in.
Be careful, son.
It fits perfectly.
Well, little diver, let's make some money.
Arkady Semyonovich, who will build the ships when we get the investment?
Who?
Our friend.
You're not my friend, you bastard.
Follow us, guys.
Come let's go.
Championship forマrsного .
What's this?
Did you hear that?
What?
Sounds...
just sounds of your международного успеха.
I think they're gone.
I'm waiting for him. I'm waiting for him.
Where are you?
Nikita? Earthlings?
No.
Mother of God! I'm here! I'm here! Mother of Nikita!
I'm here! I'm here!
Nikita, he locked me up!
Nikita, we're listening.
Grandpa, come in. We need your help, urgently!
I hear strange noises.
I hope you're my mother.
We've prepared ourselves.
Because now you'll see what will change the life of our whole country.
Let's see.
What? How?
Wait, wait, wait.
Nikita! My friends! I'm so glad to see you!
Wait, how are you? Didn't they hurt you?
Did it hurt? It hurt a lot. Because I missed you.
Okay, run. And I haven't untwisted the part yet.
Okay.
Turn it around.
I think the fish is stinking.
Let's check.
What's this?
A cake.
There was no cake on the plate.
And this is a surprise. A compliment from the chef.
So bring the surprise.
The waiter. The waiters will cut it.
Don't cut it. The cream is very tender. We'll do it ourselves.
Uh-huh.
Your beard has opened.
Thank you.
Bring it.
So, comrades, let's continue the movement.
What's wrong with you?
Here. I can't do it.
You need to pump yourself up, Nikita.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome!
Arkadiy Semyonovich Ladapa!
One moment.
Turn it on.
Dear friends.
Each of us has a dream.
Someone dreams of becoming a ballerina.
Someone dreams of becoming an engineer.
But personally, I always dreamed of flying.
Flying?
You always dreamed of cutting money for state orders.
But as we all know, a dream won't come true on its own.
For its realization, you need to work long and persistently.
He wrote his speech on VKontakte.
Thanks to the persistent work of your humble servant,
soon every resident of the Black Sea coast
will be able to use the service of a flying taxi.
Well, I hope it will be possible,
provided we get enough money.
Nikita, it's all gone.
We won't make it in time.
Let's go.
No.
Ladies and gentlemen, let's welcome my unique invention!
Thank you very much.
My pleasure.
Thank you.
Where is your persistent Chairman Kim Jong Il of China?
Come on in.
It'll be much better in no time.
Congratulations.
Sit down.
She's funny.
Did you all get it?
Yes.
Excuse me.
You can ask anything you want, Ye GPUKAN.
What?
What did you order?
I was perfect.
Oh.
You are called attention and we beg your forgiveness in a hurry.
Come here.
One, two, three.
Thank you.
Do you think they made it?
I don't see them.
Let's go.
We made it.
We have a little technical problem.
We'll fix it now.
Eat while the sandwiches...
Drink some lemonade...
Listen to some music...
Anthrax!
Take them.
Take it.
There is some lousy things there.
Nina, go out, please.
I'm there.
Concert is over.
The director of the company is a fraud.
He made 2 billion rubles, but did not make the taxi.
He stole the taxi.
It's a baby.
Who stole it?
The competitors.
Ask him what principle the ship works on,
what fuel, what speed.
Why didn't the ship take off?
Because he stole it! It's not his ship!
No, please! I didn't say anything!
Who is it?
Who is she?
Call in!
Hi!
It's from an expensive multimedicine doll.
For five thousand rubles.
Warrior!
One thousandلة
EPISODE 1
Well, now everything will be fine for sure.
And you will remember this moment forever.
One moment.
Nikita, I have an idea.
Do you remember about the diminution?
Look.
I'll show you now.
Let's go.
What's going on?
Nikita, follow me.
Dad, this is our chance.
Run faster.
Good luck, Kurakaki.
See you at home.
Roger that.
Be careful.
Good luck.
Kumai!
Have you heard that?
No one wants to visit Couple's house only.
I didn't know that we could meet so well in silence.
It feels so wonderful in my mind.
Yes, it does.
It really feels better here.
You know, Stunt, this is my first flight. I've never been on a plane before.
And here's a spaceship! Thank you, Stunt!
Hey, hey! Easy, easy! Be careful, Ikita!
Be careful, or we'll fall into the swamp again!
The End
Well, Semyonovs, now it's our turn.
Thank you, fellow earthlings.
I think I understood what I was waiting for.
Meeting you.
I am grateful that you accepted me into your family.
And family is a great power.
Much more than a step.
What? Will you come to us again?
I'll try, Nikita.
But I don't know when.
Nikita, it's time to let go of a friend.
I'm waiting.
Goodbye.
Goodbye. I'll miss you.
Well, let's go, Semyonovs.
Long wires, long tears.
Goodbye, Semyonovs.
Goodbye, Nikita.
Goodbye.
So what, Alya?
This is my new room.
You see how the kids hung around?
Beautiful.
So.
I love you so much.
Things are going well for us. Mikhail has finally found a new job.
And now he is the boss himself.
Katya is now a journalist.
But not a real one, of course, she is just an intern for now.
But she is trying very hard.
Hello, I am reporter Katya Semyonova in the new special column
Life of our city.
Tell me, do you live here or have you come to rest?
We have been here for three days and we like it very much.
Nikita has found a girl for himself.
He has been sucking on her for three years.
And finally he got out of it and invited me to ride a bike.
All in me.
And I finally made my own space radio station.
And now Semyonova and I are always in touch with the Universe.
Goga, I just want to say hello to you.
I am fine.
Very good.
For a comfortable space trip I am giving you a musical hippie.
And I will sing a song for you.
Sing!
Cosmodrome
For me it is an icy blue
And we will dream of grass, grass, grass
Green, green grass
GRESS
I have landed in another planet
I have eaten grandpa all the sweets
Become my friend between the galaxies
We were hiding it from the agents, and they are still looking for it.
It's so cute and a little shabby. Who are these guys?
I'm waiting.
Waiting, waiting.
Waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting, waiting.
I'm waiting.
Left.
Right.
We're sitting.
Waiting.
I'm waiting.
Left.
Right.
Down.
Up.
Let's shake the Broom!
Lower it!
I'm waiting.
Waiting, waiting.
Hands up!
I'm waiting.
Shaking, shaking.
Cockroach.
I'm waiting.
Shaking, shaking.
Cockroach.
I'm waiting.
Let's shake the Broom!
I'm waiting, I know how to wait!
I'm waiting
Left
Right
Down
Up
Tired
I'm waiting
Left
Right
Down
Up
Tired
I'm waiting
Left
Right
Down
Up
Tired
I'm waiting
Hands up
Swing
Crick
Crack
Room
I'm waiting
Splitting
Crack
Room